- [Pimp C] Man don't do it.
I'm tellin' you don't do it.
- [Man 1] Mm-mm.
- [Pimp C] Don't do it.
- [Man 2] He's already nervous man.
- [DJ Paul] The only
thing I wanna know is,
why is he dressed like Rowdie Piper?
- [Andre 3000] I got
Scottish in my family.
- [Bun B] Scottish?
- Come on man.
- So who's your bridesmaid?
- Come on man. Support me.
Support me. Come on now.
When the man is ready, he ready.
When y'all get 80, 70, 60, 55
years old and y'all gonna be
sitting in a rocking chair by yourself to
"Ahh, let's go to the club.
Let's go to the club."
Y'all gonna be the only
old (silence) in the club.
- Seriously, Dre, all playing aside man.
Why get married pimpin'? Why?
♪ So I typed a text to
a girl I used to see ♪
♪ Sayin' that I chose this
cutie pie with whom I wanna be ♪
♪ And I apologize if this
message gets you down ♪
♪ Then I CC'ed every girl
that I'd see-see 'round town ♪
♪ And hate to see y'all frown, ♪
♪ but I'd rather see her smilin' ♪
♪ Wetness all around me,
true, but I'm no island ♪
♪ Peninsula, maybe ♪
♪ It makes no sense, I know crazy ♪
♪ Give up all this (silence)
cat that's in my lap. ♪
♪ No lookin' back ♪
♪ Spaceships don't come equipped
with rear view mirrors ♪
♪ They dip as quick as they can ♪
♪ The atmosphere is now ripped ♪
♪ I'm so like a pimp,
I'm glad it's night ♪
♪ So the light from the sun ♪
♪ Would not burn me on my bum ♪
♪ When I shoot the moon ♪
♪ High jump the broom ♪
♪ Like a preemie out the womb ♪
♪ My partner yellin'
"Too soon! Don't do it! ♪
♪ Reconsider! Read some
liter-ature on the subject ♪
♪ You sure? (silence) it. ♪
♪ You know we got your
back like chiroprac-tic ♪
♪ If that (silence) do you dirty ♪
♪ We'll wipe her (silence)
out in some detergent ♪
♪ Now hurry hurry ♪
♪ Go on to the altar ♪
♪ I know you ain't a pimp, ♪
♪ but pimp remember what I taught ya ♪
♪ Keep your heart, three
stacks, keep your heart ♪
♪ Hey keep your heart, three
♪ Man these girls is
smart, three stacks, ♪
♪ these girls is smart ♪
♪ Play your part, play your part ♪
♪ My (silence) a choosy lover ♪
♪ Never (silence) without a rubber ♪
♪ Never in the sheets, like
it on top of the cover ♪
♪ Money on the dresser,
drive a Kompressor ♪
♪ Top notch (silence) get
the most, not the lesser ♪
♪ Trash like to (silence)
with $40 in the club ♪
♪ (silence) up the game,
(silence) it gets no love ♪
♪ She be cross-country,
givin' all that she got ♪
♪ A thousand a pop, I'm
pullin' Bentleys off the lot ♪
♪ I smashed up the gray
one, bought me a red ♪
♪ Every time we hit the
parkin' lot we turn head ♪
♪ Some (silence) wanna choose
but them (silence) too scary ♪
♪ Your (silence) chose me, you
ain't a pimp, you a (silence) ♪
♪ I choose you, girl ♪
♪ Baby you been rollin' solo,
time to get down with the team ♪
♪ The grass is greener
on that other side, ♪
♪ if know what I mean ♪
♪ I show you (silence) you never seen, ♪
♪ the Seven Wonders of the World ♪
♪ And I can make you the eighth
if you wanna be my girl ♪
♪ When I say my girl I
don't mean my woman, ♪
♪ that ain't my style ♪
♪ Need a real street stalker
to walk a green mile ♪
♪ We pilin' up the paper
on the dinin' room table ♪
♪ Cuz you able to realize I'm
the truth and not a fable ♪
♪ We rock the freshest Sable,
keep that 'chilla on the rack ♪
♪ What I look like with some
thousand dollar (silence) ♪
♪ up on my back? ♪
♪ I'm a million dollar mack
that need a billion dollar ♪
(silence)
♪ Put my pimpin' in your life,
watch ya daddy get rich ♪
♪ Easy as A-B-C, simple as 1-2-3 ♪
♪ Get down with U-G-K, Pimp C, B-U-N B ♪
♪ Cuz what's a (silence) with no pimp? ♪
♪ And what's a pimp with no (silence) ♪
♪ Don't be a lame, you know
the game and how it goes ♪
♪ We tryin' to get chose ♪
♪ I choose you, girl ♪
♪ Eeny meeny decisions,
with precision I pick or ♪
♪ Make my selection on who
I choose to be with girl ♪
♪ Don't touch my protection,
I know you want it to slip ♪
♪ But slippin' is somethin' I
don't do, tippin' for life ♪
♪ That's like makin' it rain
every month on schedule ♪
♪ Let me tell you, get
your parasol umbrella ♪
♪ Cuz it's gonna get wetter ♪
♪ Better prepare ya for the C support ♪
♪ She supposed to spend it on
that baby but we see she don't ♪
♪ Ask-ask Paul McCartney ♪
♪ The lawyers couldn't stop me ♪
♪ Slaughter-slaughterin' them pockets ♪
♪ Had to tie her to a rocket ♪
♪ Send her in to outer space,
I know he wish he could ♪
♪ Cuz he payin' 20K a day,
that (silence) is eating good ♪
♪ Like an infant on a double D
(silence) just getting plump ♪
♪ Cuz you miscalculated the
next to the-the last pump ♪
♪ Dump-dump in the gut,
(silence) from the giddy up ♪
♪ Better choose the right one
or pick-pick the kiddies up ♪
♪ I choose you, girl ♪
♪ I choose you, baby ♪
(music fades)